<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UN-Toxic</string>
    <string name="pro">Verifying Your Profile !!</string>
    <string name="enter_your_phone_no">Enter Your Phone No.</string>
    <string name="get_otp">Get OTP</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify OTP</string>
    <string name="etn">Enter Your Name</string>
    <string name="npds">No. of Smoke Per Day -</string>
    <string name="nofsmoke">TextView</string>
    <string name="nofdr">No of Glass(250ml) Per Day -</string>
    <string name="noofdrinks">TextView</string>
    <string name="entp">Enter Your Phone No.</string>
    <string name="drinking">Drinking</string>
    <string name="smoking">Smoking</string>
    <string name="conitnue">Conitnue</string>
    <string name="enter_no">Enter Number of Cigarettes Per Day</string>
    <string name="title_activity_homepage">Homepage</string>
    <string name="title_home">Progress</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Rewards</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Tips</string>
    <string name="pricepersm">Price Per Cigratte</string>
    <string name="tip1">Constant Changes Required</string>
    <string name="set_the_goal">Set Goal</string>
    <string name="Goal">Goal : </string>
    <string name="Cost">Cost : </string>
    <string name="money_reserved">Money Saved</string>
    <string name="rve">Rewards Earned</string>
    <string name="numberofsmokes">Number of Smoke Free</string>
    <string name="bigquestion">How Much Money You will Save ??</string>
    <string name="week">1 Week</string>
    <string name="month">1 Month</string>
    <string name="months6">6 Months</string>
    <string name="year">1 Year</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="tip2"> Every time you light a Cigarette, you are saying your life isnt worth living</string>
    <string name="tip3">Smoking is Habit that kills your pocket as well as your health, so choose wise choose smart</string>
    <string name="tips4">Quit Smoking or Die Trying</string>
    <string name="tip5">Don\'t mistake pleasure for Happiness, after all salt and sugar look the same.</string>
    <string name="tip6">You are Fool if you think smoking is Cool</string>
    <string name="tip7">Health and Wealth after you start smoking - Save Us today and We\'ll save you later</string>
    <string name="tip8"><b>Every year 8 million people leave smoking, not because they quit on smoking, but because life quits on them</b></string>
    <string name="btneffect">EFFECTS OF SMOKING</string>




    <string name="affirmation1"><b>There are no proven ways to reverse the clock, but there is one known way to look older than your years,
        start smoking. Smoking can change your appearance by altering your teeth, hair, and skin. Aside from your appearance, smoking weakens your heart,
        lungs, and bones; and reduces fertility.
        Look at these two photos. One of these identical twins is a smoker; the other is not. Can you spot the difference?</b></string>


    <string name="affirmation2">Oral cancer risk is also elevated in people who smoke or use smokeless tobacco.
        Adding alcohol to the mix intensifies this risk; those who smoke and are heavy drinkers have a 15-fold increased risk of oral cancer.
        Oral cancer usually starts as a sore inside the mouth that wont go away. Quitting smoking lowers the risk of oral cancer.</string>


    <string name="affirmation3">Nine out of every 10 deaths from lung cancer are due to smoking, meaning that 90% of lung cancer deaths could be prevented.
        Smoking causes other lung problems, like emphysema, and increases the risk of contracting pneumonia.</string>


    <string name="affirmation4">While the effects of smoking on the lungs are widely understood,
        it might surprise some smokers to know that they are also damaging their bones. Smoking raises the risk of osteoporosis and fractures.
        Fractures of the spine can cause an abnormal curvature and "hunchback" appearance.</string>



    <string name="affirmation5">The outside eye wrinkles affectionately termed "crows feet" develop earlier in smokers than in nonsmokers.
        These wrinkles also tend to be deeper in those who smoke. Squinting to keep smoke out of your eyes only worsens the tendency to develop wrinkles around the eyes.
        On top of all this, there is damage to the internal skin components because of the lack of nutrient and oxygen delivery to the skin.</string>


    <string name="affirmation6">Yellow teeth are an obvious sign of smoking.
        But smokers experience other oral and dental problems as well. Gum disease,
        bad breath, and tooth loss are all more common in people who smoke.

</string>


    <string name="affirmation7">Smoking can worsen the natural process of hair thinning that occurs as we age.
        Some research shows that baldness is more common in men who smoke;
        studies from Taiwan show that male-pattern baldness risk increases in Asian men who smoke.</string>


    <string name="affirmation8">Tobacco stains the skin of the nails and hands. This can be a telltale
        sign of a chronic smoker. Fortunately, this discoloration usually fades after you have stopped smoking.</string>


    <string name="affirmation9">Cataracts are opaque areas on the lens of the eye that interfere with vision.
        Effective treatment can mean that surgery is required. Smoking increases the likelihood that you will develop cataracts.</string>


    <string name="affirmation10">Smokers also have an increased risk of getting psoriasis, an unsightly and often uncomfortable skin condition.
        Psoriasis is characterized by thick, scaly skin patches that are most commonly seen on the elbows, scalp, hands, back, or feet.</string>

    <string name="affirmation11">
        Narrowing of the coronary arteries of the heart is one of the most dangerous consequences of smoking.
        Since smoking also raises blood pressure and makes blood more likely to clot, the risk of a heart attack is dramatically increased.
        Smoking can also affect blood flow in other ways. Erectile dysfunction is one consequence of altered blood flow in men who smoke.

    </string>


    <string name="title">TITLE</string>
    <string name="title1"><b>Which Twin Smokes?</b></string>
    <string name="title2"><b>Oral Cancer</b></string>
    <string name="title3"><b>Lung Cancer</b></string>
    <string name="title4"><b>Brittle BonesO</b></string>
    <string name="title5"><b>Eye Wrinkles (Crow Feet)</b></string>
    <string name="title6"><b>Damaged Gums and Teeth</b></string>
    <string name="title7"><b>Hair Loss</b></string>

    <string name="title8"><b>Damaged Gums and Teeth</b></string>
    <string name="title9"><b>Cataracts</b></string>
    <string name="title10"><b>Psoriasis</b></string>
    <string name="title11"><b>Heart Disease and ED</b></string>
    <string name="update_profile">Update Profile</string>


</resources>